[{"answer": "I haven't heard -- I have seen those same reports but I'm not able to confirm, you know, directly whether that has happened.", "docId": "121029pmt", "aSentId": 42, "question": "Have you heard about that?", "qSentId": 41}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "121029pmt", "aSentId": 56, "question": "What can you tell me?", "qSentId": 55}, {"answer": "This crane on 57th Street.", "docId": "121029pmt", "aSentId": 70, "question": "Did you?", "qSentId": 69}, {"answer": "I think they are -- the most recent update I have heard, and that can certainly change, is that although they were going to try to walk up the stairs of the building, that they were not particularly confident that given the high winds that they would be able to necessarily secure it in any way.", "docId": "121029pmt", "aSentId": 76, "question": "Do you have an update for us on what the plan is for this?", "qSentId": 75}, {"answer": "The only confirmed fatality I have is the 30-year-old man who was hit by a tree.", "docId": "121029pmt", "aSentId": 85, "question": "Are you able to confirm how many people may have lost their lives in New York tonight?", "qSentId": 84}, {"answer": "Well, looking at the pictures and everything else, what I believe happened is that the crane operator and the supervision on the job did not follow the manufacturer's recommendation.", "docId": "121029pmt", "aSentId": 97, "question": "How has this been able to happen given we had nearly a week of warning that this huge storm was coming?", "qSentId": 96}, {"answer": "Absolutely it could happen.", "docId": "121029pmt", "aSentId": 111, "question": "Could that happen?", "qSentId": 110}, {"answer": "Well, Piers, the story here is without question, flooding.", "docId": "121029pmt", "aSentId": 137, "question": "What are you experiencing?", "qSentId": 136}, {"answer": "Well, we were talking to the mayor of Atlantic City on air earlier, and I had asked him, I said look, 3:00, 4:00 in the afternoon, what do you do if you haven't left, because the roads have started to become overtopped and he said at that point, if you're not out, stay where you are, get to high ground.", "docId": "121029pmt", "aSentId": 190, "question": "What can you tell me about that and how much of a problem will that be for the mayor, if indeed people do get trapped and potentially lose their lives?", "qSentId": 189}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "121029pmt", "aSentId": 206, "question": "Have you ever seen anything quite like this?", "qSentId": 205}, {"answer": "You know, we're experiencing an epic, unprecedented and unpredictable storm in Newark right now.", "docId": "121029pmt", "aSentId": 257, "question": "What is it like where you are?", "qSentId": 256}, {"answer": "That's exactly right.", "docId": "121029pmt", "aSentId": 269, "question": "Is it simply just stay at home, batten down the hatches and wait?", "qSentId": 268}, {"answer": "Well, it's incredible.", "docId": "121029pmt", "aSentId": 297, "question": "What do you make of what we're seeing here?", "qSentId": 296}, {"answer": "Well, we're faring pretty well.", "docId": "121029pmt", "aSentId": 329, "question": "How are you fairing over there?", "qSentId": 328}, {"answer": "From what I can see, I believe so.", "docId": "121029pmt", "aSentId": 339, "question": "From everything you're seeing and reading and hearing tonight, do you think that generally the authorities have prepared well enough for this?", "qSentId": 338}, {"answer": "We're going into day three plus for some of our people down in southeast Virginia.", "docId": "121029pmt", "aSentId": 360, "question": "How bad are things there?", "qSentId": 359}, {"answer": "I mean, this is the first disaster I've gone through in New York City.", "docId": "121029pmt", "aSentId": 380, "question": "Are you concerned still?", "qSentId": 379}, {"answer": "I mean, it's pretty incredible, Piers.", "docId": "121029pmt", "aSentId": 481, "question": "What does that do to the financial system?", "qSentId": 480}, {"answer": "Well, obviously we knew this was possible.", "docId": "121029pmt", "aSentId": 510, "question": "What do you make of it?", "qSentId": 509}, {"answer": "Yes, take a look at this.", "docId": "121029pmt", "aSentId": 520, "question": "Ali, what can you tell me?", "qSentId": 519}, {"answer": "Well, it's very interesting, not only is this hurricane -- Super Storm Sandy stealing Halloween from some people, the end of the month is very important worldwide for traders, for fund managers, for hedge fund managers, because everyone is judged monthly on their performance.", "docId": "121029pmt", "aSentId": 544, "question": "What do you think that will do to the financial markets?", "qSentId": 543}, {"answer": "Well, generally speaking, the measurement for the job numbers is taken in a week and it's earlier.", "docId": "121029pmt", "aSentId": 554, "question": "And if so, what impact can this all have on the election?", "qSentId": 553}]